// export all QAs for a particular product

export const QAData = [
    {
        id: "1",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "Which side finger print support ?",
        answer: "In display fingerprint.",
        likes: 60,
        dislikes: 15,
    },

    {
        id: "2",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "Is finger print available ?",
        answer: "Yes",
        likes: 20,
        dislikes: 8,
    },

    {
        id: "3",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "How's the gaming performance ?",
        answer: "Outstanding Speed Smooth Gaming: 60+ FPS Long Battery Life Highly Recommended for Gamers.",
        likes: 20,
        dislikes: 2,
    },

    {
        id: "4",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "Is this phone waterproof ir not ?",
        answer: "It comes with an IP65 rating.",
        likes: 25,
        dislikes: 15,
    },

    {
        id: "5",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "Is 1 sim 1 memory support ?",
        answer: "No only 2 sim support not memory slot.",
        likes: 98,
        dislikes: 8,
    },

    {
        id: "6",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "Is that Dolby Atmos sound ?",
        answer: "Yes",
        likes: 22,
        dislikes: 5,
    },

    {
        id: "7",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "Does it have xpandable storage ?",
        answer: "No",
        likes: 2,
        dislikes: 2,
    },

    {
        id: "8",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "Is it suitable for wireless charging ?",
        answer: "No",
        likes: 12,
        dislikes: 5,
    },

    {
        id: "9",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "How many Os update given in this phone ?",
        answer: "2 Years of OS update and 3 Years of security update.",
        likes: 122,
        dislikes: 24,
    },

    {
        id: "10",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "Does it support 4k resolution ?",
        answer: "Yes",
        likes: 0,
        dislikes: 0,
    },

    {
        id: "11",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "How much zoom of the camera ?",
        answer: "5x",
        likes: 6,
        dislikes: 0,
    },

    {
        id: "12",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "Is there is NFC ?",
        answer: "Yes",
        likes: 0,
        dislikes: 1,
    },

    {
        id: "13",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "Curved display or not ?",
        answer: "Yes",
        likes: 1,
        dislikes: 0,
    },

    {
        id: "14",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "Is tamper glass incuded ?",
        answer: "Yes",
        likes: 103,
        dislikes: 13,
    },

    {
        id: "15",
        product_id: "1",
        question: "1 to 100% charging time",
        answer: "60 min",
        likes: 45,
        dislikes: 19,
    },
]